butcherbox.com 2019-02-07

# Privacy Policy - ButcherBox

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR BUTCHERBOX, LLC**

Effective Date: 7/1/2018

Last Updated: 7/1/2018

Thank you for using ButcherBox, LLC.  This Privacy Policy describes how information about you is collected, used and shared by ButcherBox, LLC and our subsidiaries and other affiliates (collectively, “ButcherBox,” “we,” “us” or “our”) when you access or use the websites, mobile applications or blogs provided by us (collectively, the “Sites”) or otherwise interact with us.  **  By using or accessing the Sites in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent to our collection, use, and sharing of your information in the following ways. If you do not consent, you may not use the Sites.**

We’re constantly working to improve our Sites, so ButcherBox reserves the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in our sole discretion.  If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will provide notice of such changes, such as by sending an email notification, providing notice through the Sites or updating the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.  We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you use or access the Sites or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. If you use the Sites after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes.  Remember, your use of the Sites is at all times subject to the Terms of Use, which incorporates this privacy policy and is available at <https://www.butcherbox.com/terms-of-use/>.  Any terms we use in this Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the [Terms of Use](https://www.butcherbox.com/terms-of-use/).

**1\. What does this Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Sites.  We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Sites, including to personalize, provide, and improve our services, to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you and allow other users to contact you for marketing and other purposes, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to analyze how you use the Sites.  In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties, but only as described below.

We are proud of our Sites and we strive to ensure that they do not offend people of any age. However, our Sites are not intended for children or minors under the age of thirteen years without the permission of a parent or guardian. If you believe that a child has submitted Personal Information on or through one of our Sites without the consent and supervision of a parent or guardian, please contact us using the information provided below so that we can take appropriate action.

**2\. Collection of Information.**

2.1 Information You Provide to Us.  We receive and store information you manually provide directly to us.  For example, we collect information when you register for a ButcherBox account, sign up for a subscription, participate in any interactive features of the Sites, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in a survey, contest, promotion or event, order or purchase (either for yourself or for another person) meal ingredients or other products made available through the Sites (collectively, the “Products”), apply for a job, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us.  Certain information may be required to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features.  The types of information we may collect from you include (but are not necessarily limited to):  
(a) Account information, such as your name, email address, password, postal address, phone number, subscription, delivery and dietary preferences and any other information you choose to provide;  
(b) Transaction information, such as information about the Products you purchase, shipping and delivery information and information related to returns, refunds and cancellations.  We may also collect and store limited payment information from you, such as payment card type and expiration date and the last four digits of your payment card number; however, we do not collect or store full payment card numbers and all transactions are processed by our third party payment processor;  
(c) Information about others, such as the names and email addresses of gift recipients when you purchase gifts through the Sites or invite friends or family to try the Sites or Products.  
(d) Other information you choose to provide, such as when you participate in a survey, contest, promotion or interactive area of the Sites or when you request technical or customer support.  
2.2 Information We Collect Automatically.  When you access or use the Sites, the types of information we may automatically collect about you include:  
(a) Log Information:  When you visit the Sites, our servers automatically record certain log file information, such as your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, operating system, browser type and language, referring URLs, access times, pages viewed, links clicked and other information about your activities on the Sites;   
(b) Mobile Device Information:  We collect information about the mobile device you use to access or use the Sites, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information and information about your use of our mobile applications.  With your consent, we may also collect information about the location of your device and access and collect information from certain native applications on your device (such as your device’s camera, photo album and phonebook applications) to facilitate your use of certain features of the Sites.  For more information about how you can control the collection of location information and/or our access to other applications on your device, please see “Your Choices” below; and   
(c) Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:  We and our service providers use various tracking technologies, including cookies and web beacons, to collect information about you when you interact with our Sites, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior.  Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve the Sites and your experience, see which areas and features of the Sites are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in the Sites or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness.  For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.   
2.3  **Information We Collect From Other Sources**.  We may also obtain information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect through the Sites.  For example, we may collect information about you when you post content to our pages or feeds on third party social media sites, or if you use credentials (e.g., username and password) from a third party site to create or log into your ButcherBox account.

**3\. Use of Information.  **

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

(a) Provide, maintain and improve the Sites and Products;  
(b) Manage your account and send you related information, including confirmations, updates, technical notices, security alerts and support and administrative messages;  
(c) Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;  
(d) Communicate with you about the Sites, Products, recipes, services, offers, surveys, events and other news and information we think may be of interest to you;  
(e) Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with the Sites;  
(f) Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of ButcherBox and others;  
(g) Personalize and improve the Sites and provide advertisements, content and features that match your profile or interests;  
(h) Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;  
(i) Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with a better experience; and  
(j) Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.  
ButcherBox is based in the United States, and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law.  By accessing or using the Sites or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

**4\. Sharing of Information.  **  
We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

(a) With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;  
(b) From time to time, we may share your information with selected third parties (other than our vendors) for their own marketing purposes. Before doing so, however, we may offer you the opportunity to “opt out” or “opt in” as required by applicable law.  
(c) When you participate in the interactive areas of the Sites or interact with us on third party social media sites, certain information that you provide may be displayed publicly, such as your name, photos and other information you choose to provide;  
(d) In response to a request for information if we reasonably believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, rule, regulation or legal process;  
(e) If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our Terms of Use or other policies, or to protect the rights, property or safety of ButcherBox or others;  
(f) Your information may be transferred to a successor organization if, for example, we transfer the ownership or operation of the Sites to another organization, if we merge with or are acquired by another organization, or if we liquidate our assets; your information may also be transferred to a third party in connection with negotiations related to a merger, acquisition, or liquidation.  
(g) Between and among ButcherBox and any current or future parent, subsidiary and/or affiliated company; and  
(h) With your consent or at your direction.  
We also may share aggregated, anonymized, or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.  

**5\. Social Sharing Features.  **  
The Sites may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools, such as the Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest buttons (e.g., “Like,” “Tweet” and “Pin It”), which let you share actions you take on the Sites with other media.  Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

**6\. Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others Interest-Based Ads.  **  
In addition to the cookies we deliver to your computer or mobile device through our Sites, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our Sites. Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors across nonaffiliated websites and delivering targeted advertisements either on our Sites or on other websites.

You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on our Sites. For example, if you don’t want information about your visit to our Sites sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking here. Please note that the Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to us.

In addition, if you would like to opt out of having participating entities track your online behavior for advertising purposes when you are browsing our Sites, click here for a “Website Opt Out.” You will be directed to an industry-developed website that allows you to choose whether each listed entity may collect and use data for interest-based advertising purposes. It may be that some of the third parties that collect interest-based information on our Sites do not participate in the Website Opt Out, in which case the best way to avoid third party tracking of your online behaviors may be through your browser settings and deletion of cookies.  

The Website Opt Out described above works only on websites. To opt out of having participating entities track your behaviors for advertising purposes when you are using a mobile application, download and use the Digital Advertising Alliance’s “App Choices” app. As with the Website Opt Out, the “Mobile App Opt Out” prevents tracking only by participating entities.  

Please note that the Website Opt Out and Mobile App Opt Out are device specific. If you wish to opt-out from having interest-based information collected by participating entities across all devices, you need take the steps outlined above from each device.  

**7\. Customized Ad Campaigns.  **  
We may also work with third party social media sites, such as Facebook, to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign, unless you notify us that you prefer not to have information about you used in this way.  For more information about how you can opt out of customized campaigns, please see “Your Choices” below.

**8\. Information Collected From Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy.  **  
Through cookies we place on your browser or device, we may collect information about your online activity after you leave our Sites.  Just like any other usage information we collect, this information allows us to improve the Sites and customize your online experience, and otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy.  Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites.  Our Sites do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we may collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Sites and after you leave our Sites.

**9\. Affiliated Businesses.  **  
In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell or provide products or services to you through or in connection with the Sites (either alone or jointly with us).  You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service.  We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business’ or websites’ policies.

**10\. Security.  **  
Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security.  If you access your account via a third party site or service (such as by logging in via a Facebook or other third party site or service), you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service.  You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

ButcherBox takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.  Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to or from us over the Internet.  In particular, email sent to or from the Sites may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Additionally, unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our Terms of Use (located at <https://www.butcherbox.com/terms-of-use/>) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of ButcherBox, our employees, our users, or others.  

**11\. Your Choices.  **  
You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features.

11.1 Account Information.  You may add, update, correct or modify information about you at any time by logging into your online account or by emailing us at [support@butcherbox.com](mailto:support@butcherbox.com).  The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Sites change.  If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us by email at [[legal@butcherbox.com](mailto:legal@butcherbox.com)].  When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.   
11.2 Account Deactivation.  If you wish to deactivate your account, please email us at [support@butcherbox.com](mailto:support@butcherbox.com), but note we may continue to store information about you as required or permitted by law or for legitimate business purposes.  We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it.    
11.3 Location Information.  With your consent, we may collect information about your actual location when you use our mobile applications.  You may stop the collection of this information at any time by changing the settings on your mobile device, but note that some features of our mobile applications may no longer function if you do so.  
11.4 Cookies.  If you prefer, you can set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies.  Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Sites. For more information about how to control placement of cookies on your computer or device, including those used for online behavioral advertising, see above.

**12\. Contact Us.**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@butcherbox.com](mailto:legal@butcherbox.com) and we will try to resolve your concerns.
